let's look at the answer for her heat
time quiz in a well-designed cache hit
time is significantly lower than Miss
time miss time includes the hit time and
the Miss penalty typically we want the
hit time to be very small and that means
that the Miss time should not be
anywhere close to the hit time and if
there is any miss penalty miss time will
be larger than hit time anyway so this
should be true for every cache even if
you didn't design it very well hit time
is larger than the Miss penalty we
definitely don't want that the Miss
penalty is the memory access time if our
hit time is similar to that or larger
than that then the cache is not gonna be
useful at all so this should not be
selected hit time equals to the Miss
penalty no we want the hit time to be
significantly less than the Miss penalty
if it is equal to the Miss penalty we
might just as well go to memory every
time because that's what the Miss
penalty is about so we should not select
this and finally miss time larger than
the Miss penalty Miss time is equal to
the hit time plus the Miss penalty which
means that the Miss time should always
be larger than the Miss penalty anyway
so this is true for every cache not only
a well designed one as we can see for a
cache to be beneficial it needs to have
a low hit time in fact in a
well-designed cache we can say that the
hit time is much less than miss time
while the Miss time and Miss penalty
should be similar to each other because
the hit time is so small and the
difference between the two is the hit
time